[
  {
    "front": "개",
    "back": "Dog",
    "enabled": true
  },
  {
    "front": "고양이",
    "back": "Cat",
    "enabled": true
  },
  {
    "front": "물고기",
    "back": "Fish",
    "enabled": true
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "새",
    "back": "Bird"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "말",
    "back": "Horse"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "쥐",
    "back": "Mouse"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "기린",
    "back": "Giraffe"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "소",
    "back": "Cow"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "원숭이",
    "back": "Monkey"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "돼지",
    "back": "Pig"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "토끼",
    "back": "Rabbit"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "뱀",
    "back": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "코끼리",
    "back": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "닭",
    "back": "Chicken"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "강아지",
    "back": "Puppy"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "염소",
    "back": "Goat"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "양",
    "back": "Sheep"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "나비",
    "back": "Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "게",
    "back": "Crab"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "늑대",
    "back": "Wolf"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "사슴",
    "back": "Deer"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "곰",
    "back": "Bear"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "여우",
    "back": "Fox"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "너구리",
    "back": "Raccoon"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "거북이",
    "back": "Turtle"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "개구리",
    "back": "Frog"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "상어",
    "back": "Shark"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "악어",
    "back": "Crocodile"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "고래",
    "back": "Whale"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "문어",
    "back": "Octopus"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "오징어",
    "back": "Squid"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "장어",
    "back": "Eel"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "앵무새",
    "back": "Parrot"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "까마귀",
    "back": "Crow"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "비둘기",
    "back": "Dove"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "매",
    "back": "Hawk"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "사자",
    "back": "Lion"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "호랑이",
    "back": "Tiger"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "도마뱀",
    "back": "Lizard"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "개미",
    "back": "Ant"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "달팽이",
    "back": "Snail"
  },
  {
    "enabled": true,
    "front": "모기",
    "back": "Mosquito"
  }
]